A Guide to the Commonwealth Fund records, Grants, SG 3, Series 15 FA1485
Rockefeller Archive Center
Commonwealth Fund records, Grants, SG 3, Series 15
1934-2012
Rockefeller Archive Center
Commonwealth Fund
FA1485
176.73 Cubic Feet
Conditions Governing Access
Open for research. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC.
Researchers interested in accessing digital media (floppy disks, CDs, DVDs, etc.) in this collection must use an access surrogate. The original items may not be accessed because of preservation concerns. To request an access surrogate be made, or if you are unsure if there is an access surrogate, please contact an RAC archivist.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
The Commonwealth Fund records were donated to RAC in 1985. The initial transfer of archival records to RAC began in 1986, and transfers continue on a regular basis. These specific grant files were transferred to RAC in multiple accessions.
Scope and Contents
Each grant file often contains records pertaining to: budget and administration, proposals and development, articles and background information, correspondence, grant products and related program files. The material represented in this series also contains a selection of program files, program reviews and evaluations, grant authorizations and declinations.
Arrangement
Arranged in 3 subseries by record type.
- Grants and Program Files, 1982-2012; 1
  - Abt Associates, Inc. - Janet Shikles (990729), 1999 (Box 1, Folder 1-2)
  - Beth Israel Hospital - Pomeroy (980734), 1998-1999 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Alliance for Aging Research - Perry (970943), 1997-1998 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Alliance for Aging Research - Perry (970943) - Grant Products, 1997-1998 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Alliance for Aging Research - Perry (970943) - Grant Products, 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - PDF, Inc. - Fox (990197), 1998-1999 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - St. Mary's Hospital Medical School (92-66) - Grant Products, 1992-1994 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - St. Mary's Hospital Medical School (92-66) - Auxiliary File, 1990-1992 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - University of California, San Franscisco (UCSF) - Newcomer (96611) - Proposal, 1995-1996 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - University of California, San Franscisco (UCSF) - Newcomer (96611) - Background, 1995-2000 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - University of California, San Franscisco (UCSF) - Newcomer (96611) - Administration, 1995-2000 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - University of California, San Franscisco (UCSF) - Newcomer (96611) - Grant Products, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 3-4)
  - MDS Associates - Falk (980509) - Analysis of the 1998 Survey of Women's Health - Administration and Budget (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - MDS Associates - Falk (980509) - Analysis of the 1998 Survey of Women's Health - Proposal Development (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - MDS Associates - Falk (980509) - Analysis of the 1998 Survey of Women's Health - Conference Call, 1998 October 6 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - MDS Associates - Falk (980509) - Analysis of the 1998 Survey of Women's Health - Reports, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Abt Associates, Inc. (90-05) - Auxiliary File, 1990-1992 (Box 4, Folder 2-3)
  - Beth Israel Hospital (10052) - Auxiliary File, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Graduate Joint Degree Program in Nursing and Management - Administration, 1989-1991 (Box 5, Folder 2-3)
  - Graduate Joint Degree Program in Nursing and Management - Turn Downs, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 4-5)
  - Graduate Joint Degree Program in Nursing and Management - Turn Downs, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Graduate Joint Degree Program in Nursing and Management - Evaluation, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 2-3)
  - Partnership for A Drug-Free America (93-07) - Auxiliary File, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Beth Israel Hospital (93-01) - Auxiliary File, 1992-1993 (Box 7, Folder 1-2)
  - Princeton Survey Research Associates (PSRA) - Colasanto (990564) - Older Americans Health Insurance Experiences - Administration, 1999-2000 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Princeton Survey Research Associates (PSRA) - Colasanto (990564) - Older Americans Health Insurance Experiences - Questionnaire, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Princeton Survey Research Associates (PSRA) - Colasanto (990564) - Older Americans Health Insurance Experiences - Administration, Correspondence, 1999-2000 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Princeton Survey Research Associates (PSRA) - Colasanto (990564) - Older Americans Health Insurance Experiences - Grant Products, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Princeton Survey Research Associates (PSRA) - Colasanto (990564) - Older Americans Health Insurance Experiences - Grant Products, 1999-2001 (Box 8, Folder 1-2)
  - Blue Cross-Blue Shield of Kansas City - Healthy Steps for Young Children Site (20000154), 1998-2000 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Children's Hospital of Pittsburgh - Healthy Steps for Young Children Site (20000150), 1997-1999 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Massachusetts General Hospital- Healthy Steps for Young Children Site (971046), 1996-1997 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Henry Ford Health System - Healthy Steps for Young Children Site (20000153), 1996-2000 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - New York Hospital-Cornell Medical Center - Healthy Steps for Young Children Site (20000440), 1997-2000 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Amarillo Area Foundation, Inc. - Healthcare Professional Associates - Healthy Steps for Young Children Site (20000152), 1996-2000 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Columbia University - Glied (990818) - Task Force on the Future of Health Insurance, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 3-4)
  - Columbia University - Glied (990818) - Task Force on the Future of Health Insurance - Proposal Development, 1999-2000 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Columbia University - Glied (990818) - Task Force on the Future of Health Insurance, 1999-2000 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Columbia University - Glied (990818) - Task Force on the Future of Health Insurance - Grant Products, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 2-3)
  - Columbia University - Glied (990818) - Task Force on the Future of Health Insurance - Overview Charts, 1999-2000 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Economic and Social Research Institute (ESRI) - Meyer (20000441) - State and Local Initiatives to Enhance Health Coverage (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - The Lewin Group (980558) - Insuring Low Income Children and Families - Report, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - The Lewin Group (980558) - Insuring Low Income Children and Families - Administration and Background, 1998-1999 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - The Lewin Group (980558) - Insuring Low Income Children and Families - Proposal Development, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - The Lewin Group (980558) - Insuring Low Income Children and Families - Correspondence, 1998-2000 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - The Lewin Group (980558) - Insuring Low Income Children and Families - Grant Products, 1998-1999 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - The Lewin Group (980558) - Insuring Low Income Children and Families - Reports, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - The Lewin Group (980558) - Insuring Low Income Children and Families - Reports, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 1-2)
  - New York City Language Focus Groups, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Institute of Medicine (IOM) (94-22) - Correspondence, 1993-1994 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Institute of Medicine (IOM) (94-22) - Articles and Background (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Institute of Medicine (IOM) (94-22) - Grant Products, 1993-1994 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - An Integrated Approach to Quality of Care - Meeting, 1993 May 25 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - An Integrated Approach to Quality of Care - Meeting, 1993 October 21-22 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - An Integrated Approach to Quality of Care - Meeting, 1993 August 26-27 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Darmouth - Depression in Women Survey (96260) (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - 96955 - Cher - Mitchell - Correspondence, 1996 July (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - 96964 - UCSD - Kronick - Proposal, 1996 July (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - 96964 - UCSD - Kronick - Administration and Budget (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - 96964 - UCSD - Kronick - Correspondence, 1996 July (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - 96964 - UCSD - Kronick - Grant Products, 1996 July (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - 96955 - Cher - Mitchell - Proposal (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - 96955 - Cher - Mitchell - Grant Products, 1996 July (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - 96955 - Cher - Mitchell - Administration (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Interactive Video (91-38), 1990-1992 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Darmouth-Hitchcock Medical Center (96-20), 1995-1997 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Darmouth-Hitchcock Medical Center (96-20) - Meeting, 1997 November 4 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Darmouth-Hitchcock Medical Center (96-20), 1996-1998 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - National Committee for Quality Assurance (NCQA) (95-11) - Enhancing Consumer Choice of Health Plans, Phase II, 1994-1997 (Box 16, Folder 1-2)
  - National Committee for Quality Assurance (NCQA) (95-11) - Enhancing Consumer Choice of Health Plans, Phase II - Correspondence, 1994-1995 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - National Committee for Quality Assurance (NCQA) (95-11) - Enhancing Consumer Choice of Health Plans, Phase II - Final Report, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - National Academy of Sciences (NAS) - Institute of Medicine (IOM) - Shine (970264) - National Roundtable on Healthcare Quality, Year Two, 1997-1998 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - National Academy of Sciences (NAS) - Institute of Medicine (IOM) - Shine (970264) - National Roundtable on Healthcare Quality, Year Two - Proposal Development, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - National Academy of Sciences (NAS) - Institute of Medicine (IOM) - Shine (970264) - National Roundtable on Healthcare Quality, Year Two - Grant Products, 1997-2001 (Box 17, Folder 4-5)
  - National Academy of Sciences (NAS) - Institute of Medicine (IOM) - Shine (970264) - National Roundtable on Healthcare Quality, Year Two - Grant Products, 1997-1998 (Box 18, Folder 1-2)
  - Harvard Medical School - Martin (95-77), 2001 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - American Prospect - Kuttner (20000820), 2000-2001 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - The Lewin Group - Alecxih (990772), 1999 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - University of Minnesota - Women's Health Care Survey (93-70), 1993-1994 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Center for National Policy - Squaretable - Steinbruner (20010352), 2001-2002 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Global Strategy Group - Feld Focus Groups New York (990199) - Correspondence, 1998-1999 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Beth Israel Medical Center - Portenoy (990226) - Program Staff Files, 1999-2000 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Alliance for Aging Research (990769) - Grant Products, 1999 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Alliance for Aging Research (990769) - Administration and Budget, 1999-2000 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Alliance for Aging Research (990769) - Grant Products, 2000 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Alliance for Aging Research - Fifth Annual Meeting of the Paul Beeson Physician Faculty Scholars in Aging Research Program, 2000 May 6-9 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - UCLA - Brown - Access to Health Care in American Cities (970955), 1997-2001 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - UCLA - Brown - Access to Health Care in American Cities (970955) - Grant Products, 1997-2001 (Box 21, Folder 1-2)
  - Manpower Demonstration Research Corporation (MDRC) (94-25) - High School Career Academies Demonstration - Grant Products, 1996 (Box 21, Folder 3-4)
  - Johns Hopkins - School to Work Transition Program, Phase Two - Packer (95-24) (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Jobs for the Future (95449) - Grant Products, 1995-1996 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Greater Southeast Healthcare System - School to Work Transition Program, Year Three (95422) - Proposal, 1995 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Greater Southeast Healthcare System - School to Work Transition Program, Year Three (95422), 1995-1996 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Institute for Educational Leadership (95419) - American Youth Policy Forum 1995-1996, 1995-1997 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Institute for Educational Leadership (95419) - American Youth Policy Forum 1995-1996 - Grant Products (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Greater Philadelphia Sponsor-A-Scholar (SAS) Program, Phase Six (96147), 1995-1997 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Greater Philadelphia Sponsor-A-Scholar (SAS) Program, Phase Six (96147) - Grant Products, 1996-1997 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Greater Philadelphia Sponsor-A-Scholar (SAS) Program, Phase Six (9539), 1994-1995 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Johns Hopkins - Evaluation of the Greater Southeast Community School to Work Transition Program, Phase Two (95-24), 1994-1996 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Jobs for the Future (95449) - Administration and Correspondence, 1995-1996 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Jobs for the Future (95449) - Grant Products, 1995-1996 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - States and Managed Care for Low-Income Patients (96022) - Administration and Background, 1995-1997 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - States and Managed Care for Low-Income Patients (96022) - Grant Products, 1996-2001 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - States and Managed Care for Low-Income Patients (96022) - Supplemental File (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - States and Managed Care for Low-Income Patients (96022) - Supplemental File (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - States and Managed Care for Low-Income Patients (96022) - Correspondence, 1995-2000 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Abt Associates, Inc. (990729) - Task Force on the Future of Health Insurance - Correspondence, 1999-2000 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Abt Associates, Inc. (990729) - Task Force on the Future of Health Insurance - Administration, 1998-1999 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Abt Associates, Inc. (990729) - Task Force on the Future of Health Insurance - Grant Products, 1999-2000 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Abt Associates, Inc. - Task Force on the Future of Health Insurance - Meeting Correspondence, 1999-2000 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Abt Associates, Inc. - Task Force on the Future of Health Insurance - Meetings, 1999 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Abt Associates, Inc. - Task Force on the Future of Health Insurance - Meetings, 2000 (Box 26, Folder 1-2)
  - RAND Corporation - McGlynn - Evaluation of Managed Care (970275), 1996-2001 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - RAND Corporation - McGlynn - Evaluation of Managed Care (970275) - Grant Products, 1997-2001 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - RAND Corporation - Developing a System of Health Care Quality Monitoring, Phase Three (95-42), 1994-1997 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - RAND Corporation - Developing a System of Health Care Quality Monitoring, Phase Three (95-42) - Grant Products and Payments, 1996-1997 (Box 27, Folder 1-2)
  - RAND Corporation - Health Care Quality Monitoring (94-58) - Correspondence, 1993-1996 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - RAND Corporation - Health Care Quality Monitoring (94-58) - Administration (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - RAND Corporation - Health Care Quality Monitoring (94-58) - Articles and Background (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - RAND Corporation - Health Care Quality Monitoring (94-58) - Grant Products, 1993-1994 (Box 28, Folder 1-2)
  - Health Care Quality Monitoring Meeting, 1994 March (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - National Bureau of Economic Research, Inc. (NBER) (95342) - Technology and Health Care Cost Variations, 1995-1996 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - National Bureau of Economic Research, Inc. (NBER) (95342) - Technology and Health Care Cost Variations - Grant Products, 1996 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Picker Institute (980470) - Health Care Quality and Managed Care, 1994-1999 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Picker Institute (980470) - Health Care Quality and Managed Care - Grant Products, 1998-2000 (Box 29, Folder 1-2)
  - National Committee for Quality Assurance (NCQA) (95-11) - Consumer Information Project, 1994-1995 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - National Committee for Quality Assurance (NCQA) (95-11) - Consumer Information Project - Grant Products, 1994 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - National Committee for Quality Assurance (NCQA) (95-11) - Consumer Information Project - Grant Products, 1994-1995 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - National Committee for Quality Assurance (NCQA) (95-11) - Consumer Information Project, 1994-1995 (Box 30, Folder 2-4)
  - Manpower Demonstration Research Corporation (MDRC) - Berlin (990815) - Medicaid Exit Survey, 1999-2000 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - New York University (NYU) - Newman (980662) - Dispute Resolution and Managed Care, 1998-1999 (Box 31, Folder 2-3)
  - Georgetown - Gornick (980739) - Inequalities in Health Care, 1998-2001 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Georgetown - Gornick (980739) - Inequalities in Health Care, 1998-2001 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - The Lewin Group - Stapleton (980563) - Medicare Buy-In, 1998-2000 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Brandeis - Altman (990312), 1998-2001 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Alliance for Health Reform (20000131) -Health Policy Briefings, 1999-2000 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Alliance for Health Reform (20000131) -Health Policy Briefings - Grant Products (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Alliance for Health Reform (20000131) -Health Policy Briefings - Grant Products, 2000-2001 (Box 33, Folder 1-3)
  - Alliance for Health Reform (20000131) -Health Policy Briefings - Grant Products (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Rutgers University - Cantor (20040635) - Regulatory Reform and Angiography Disparities (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Robert Wood Johnson Foundation - Schear (20030333) - Cover the Uninsured Week, 2002-2003 (Box 44, Folder 3-5)
  - Fund for the City of New York (20031181) - Public Health in New York (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Fund for the City of New York (20031241) - New York City Health Disparities Chart Book (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Greater New York Hospital Foundation - Straub (20020827) - Bioterrorism and Emergency Preparedness Education, 2002-2003 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Roger Coleman Associates - Coleman (20020217) - Reengineering Medicaid Community Offices, 2002-2003 (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - American Association of Health Plans (AAHP) - Cutler (20000458) - Promoting Health Care Collaborations to Improve Quality of Diabetes Care, 2000-2003 (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - American Association of Health Plans (AAHP) - Cutler (20000458) - Promoting Health Care Collaborations to Improve Quality of Diabetes Care - Grant Products, 1999-2002 (Box 46, Folder 1-4)
  - American Association of Health Plans (AAHP) - Cutler (20000458) - Promoting Health Care Collaborations to Improve Quality of Diabetes Care - Grant Products, 2001-2002 (Box 47, Folder 1-2)
  - Center for Health Policy Development (20040187) - Support for Implementation of Maine's Dirigo Health Plan, 2003-2004 (Box 47, Folder 3-5)
  - Center for Health Policy Development (20040187) - Support for Implementation of Maine's Dirigo Health Plan, 2003-2004 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Georgia State University - Minyard (20030683) - Assessing Community Safety Net Networks, 2003-2005 (Box 48, Folder 2-4)
  - Commonwealth Fund - Sandman (20020083) - Estimating the Costs and Consequences of Enrollment Instability in Medicaid, Child Health Plus and Family Health Plus, 2001-2003 (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - Commonwealth Fund - Sandman (20020083) - Estimating the Costs and Consequences of Enrollment Instability in Medicaid, Child Health Plus and Family Health Plus, 2001-2003 (Box 49, Folder 1-2)
  - United Hospital Fund of New York - Gould (20020116) - Evaluation of Medicaid Managed Care in New York City, 2000-2004 (Box 49, Folder 3-4)
  - United Hospital Fund of New York - Gould (20010100) - Evaluation of Medicaid Managed Care in New York City, 2000-2001, 1999-2004 (Box 50, Folder 1-4)
  - Health Research and Educational Trust - Gabel (20010107) - Employer Sponsored Health Insurance in New York, 2000-2002 (Box 50, Folder 5-6)
  - Health Research and Educational Trust - Gabel (20010107) - Employer Sponsored Health Insurance in New York, 2002 (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - Health Research and Educational Trust (20030054), 2002-2004 (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - Health Research and Educational Trust (20030054) - Grant Products, 2003-2004 (Box 51, Folder 3-4)
  - Harvard School of Public Health - Swartz (20030069), 2002-2004 (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - Harvard School of Public Health - Swartz (20030069), 2002-2004 (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - George Washington University, Center for Health Services Research and Policy (20020182) - Knitting Together Public and Private Health Insurance (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - Princeton Survey Research Associates - McIntosh (20030143) - 2003 Health Insurance Survey, 2003-2004 (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - Medicare Rights Center - Baker (20010646)- Medicare Facts and Faces, 2001-2002 (Box 52, Folder 4-5)
  - Statewide Youth Advocacy, Inc. - Ward (20020661) - Facilitated Enrollment in New York: A Report from the Field, 2002-2004 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - NuStats - Arce (20010707) - Surveying Low-Income New Yorkers About Their Health Insurance and Access to Care, 2001-2004 (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - Emory University (20020515), 2001-2004 (Box 53, Folder 3-4)
  - Georgetown - Pollitz (20030360) - Health Insurance Consumer Guide, 2003-2004 (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - Georgetown - Kofman (20030283) - Unlicensed Health Plans and Association Insolvencies (Box 54, Folder 1-3)
  - United Hospital Fund (980184) - Medicare Managed Care, 1998 (Box 54, Folder 4-5)
  - Raetzman - Authorization (20000684) (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - Blue Cross-Blue Shield Association (990214), 1998-1999 (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - Small Grants, 2001-2005 (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - Economic and Social Research Institute (ESRI) - Meyer (20010355), 2001-2003 (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - Statewide Youth Advocacy, Inc. - Ward (20000158) (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - Harvard Medical School - Newhouse (980440) - Improving the Medicare Payment System, Phase 2, 1996-2001 (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - Harvard Medical School - Newhouse (980440) - Improving the Medicare Payment System, Phase 2 (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - Kalkines, Arky, Zall and Bernstein (20000732) (Box 56, Folder 2-3)
  - Americans Over 55 At Work Program - Management Meetings, 1993 (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - Americans Over 55 At Work Program - Briefing Materials, 1992 July 15 (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - Kalkines, Arky, Zall and Bernstein (20000732) (Box 57, Folder 1-2)
  - United Hospital Fund (980184) - Medicare Managed Care (Box 57, Folder 3-4)
  - Foundation for Health Care Policy and Evaluation (FHCPE) - Leatherman (20010381) - Developing A Chartbook on Healthcare Quality in the United States (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - Foundation for Health Care Policy and Evaluation (FHCPE) - Leatherman (20010381) - Developing A Chartbook on Healthcare Quality in the United States (Box 58, Folder 1)
  - Foundation for Health Care Policy and Evaluation (FHCPE) - Leatherman (20010381) - Developing A Chartbook on Healthcare Quality in the United States - Grant Products (Box 58, Folder 2-4)
  - Consumers Union (96528) - Health and Long-Term Care Resource Guide for Seniors and their Families, 1995-2001 (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Consumers Union (96528) - Health and Long-Term Care Resource Guide for Seniors and their Families - Grant Products, 1998-2001 (Box 59, Folder 2-3)
  - Hartley (20031265) - Conference on Cost Effectiveness Analysis and Improvement in Health (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - Children's Defense Fund - Dutton (20000378) (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - Hadley and Bovbjerg (20010136) - Task Force on the Future of Health Insurance, 2000-2002 (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - The Lewin Group (20010458) - Vision 20-20 Project (Box 60, Folder 4-6)
  - National Academy of Sciences (NAS) - Institute of Medicine (IOM) - Smedley (20010316) - Understanding and Eliminating Racial and Ethnic Disparities in Health Care, 2001-2004 (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - American Heart Association - Stein (20010489) - Cardiovascular Care of Inner-City Minority Patients (Box 61, Folder 2-3)
  - Center for Health Policy Development - Riley (20010220) - Patient Safety and Medical Errors, 2000-2001 (Box 61, Folder 4)
  - Bass and Howes, Inc. - Falkenberg (20000798) - Domestic Violence Interventions, 2000-2001 (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - Bass and Howes, Inc. - Falkenberg (20000798) - Domestic Violence Interventions, 2000-2001 (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - Johns Hopkins University, School of Hygiene and Public Health - LaVeist (20000796), 2000-2001 (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - Research Foundation of the State University of New York (SUNY) - Andrulis (20000731) (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - Harvard University - Reede (20020651) - Fellowship in Minority Health Policy: Support for Program Direction and Fellowships, 2003-2004, 2002-2004 (Box 62, Folder 4)